[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the nurse in the 2000 comedy film Meet the Parents and its 2004 sequel Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "Gaylord Focker", "incorrect_answers": ["Rozalin Focker", "Pam Byrnes", "Dina Byrnes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does querulous mean?", "correct_answer": "Always complaining", "incorrect_answers": ["Always mystical", "Always dishonest", "Always asking questions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of these French writers were born before 1900 except one.", "correct_answer": "Simone de Beauvoir", "incorrect_answers": ["Alexandre Dumas", "Marcel Proust", "Gustave Flaubert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Making sugar by evaporating cane juice was developed in about 500 BC, in what country?", "correct_answer": "India", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Egypt", "Greece"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where would one find The Bridge of Eggs?", "correct_answer": "Lima , Peru", "incorrect_answers": ["Peking, China", "Sydney, Australia", "The Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie popularied the phrase Make My Day?", "correct_answer": "Sudden Impact", "incorrect_answers": ["Die Hard", "Midnight Run", "Total Recall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals usually preys on black bear cubs?", "correct_answer": "Cougar", "incorrect_answers": ["Hedgehog", "Garden snake", "Dog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Islam treat the consumption of bat meat?", "correct_answer": "Bats are forbidden food.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "All bat species are allowed to be consumed.", "Carnivorous bat species are forbidden."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This botanist taught former slaves farming techniques for self-sufficiency and is known for suggesting hundreds of uses for the peanut.", "correct_answer": "George Washington Carver", "incorrect_answers": ["Eli Whitney", "Harriet Beecher Stowe", "Abe Lincoln"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of the human body are the cords of Billroth located?", "correct_answer": "Spleen", "incorrect_answers": ["Diaphragm", "Heart", "Larynx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Steve McQueen played a bounty hunter in which popular western series that ran from 1958 to 1961?", "correct_answer": "Wanted Dead or Alive", "incorrect_answers": ["Sundance", "Have Gun Will Travel", "Rawhide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Smokey and the Bandit, Big and Little Enos offer the Bandit $80,000 to bring them what cargo within a specified time limit?", "correct_answer": "400 cases of Coors beer", "incorrect_answers": ["400 cases of Schlitz beer", "live hogs", "live chickens"]}]